const STORE = [
  {
    questionCount: 1,
    question: "What is Jerry's real name?",
    answers: [
      "Jerry",
      "Garry",
      "Larry",
      "Terry"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Garry" 
  },
  {
    questionCount: 2,
    question: "Where is Tom from?",
    answers: [
      "Libya",
      "South Carolina",
      "Canada",
      "Ohio"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "South Carolina" 
  },
  {
    questionCount: 3,
    question: "What does Ron hate more than lying?",
    answers: [
      "Europe",
      "Tammy",
      "Skim milk",
      "Frozen yogurt"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Skim milk" 
  },
  {
    questionCount: 4,
    question: "How old was Ben when he was elected mayor?",
    answers: [
      "10",
      "12",
      "15",
      "18"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "18" 
  },
  {
    questionCount: 5,
    question: "Who is Donna's famous cousin?",
    answers: [
      "R. Kelly",
      "Ginuwine",
      "User",
      "Lil' Bow Wow"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Ginuwine" 
  },
  {
    questionCount: 6,
    question: "Which of these was NOT one of Andy's band names for his band now known as Mouse Rat?",
    answers: [
      "Punch Face Champion",
      "Dog City",
      "Scarecrow Boat",
      "Three Skin"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Dog City" 
  },
  {
    questionCount: 7,
    question: "On April's 21st birthday, what does she recieve as a gift from Ron?",
    answers: [
      "A landmine",
      "A bowieknife",
      "A handgun",
      "A hand grenade"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A handgun" 
  },
  {
    questionCount: 8,
    question: "Who has NOT fallen in the pit?",
    answers: [
      "Leslie",
      "Jerry",
      "Mark",
      "Andy"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Jerry" 
  },
  {
    questionCount: 9,
    question: "What did Leslie Knope major in at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry?",
    answers: [
      "Charms",
      "Potions",
      "Transfigeration",
      "Herbology"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Potions" 
  },
  {
    questionCount: 10,
    question: "Who broke the coffee maker?",
    answers: [
      "Leslie did. She broke it",
      "April was the last one to use it",
      "Donna's been awfully quiet",
      "Ron broke it. He punched it"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Ron broke it. He punched it" 
  },
]